Panic in the Mailroom is a animation, family,
comedy film directed by Mark O'Hare.
Two Minions are busy at work in the mailroom.
One of them, bored, decides to throw a box of expired
PX-41 samples into its designated chute.
Ken the Minion / Mike the Minion (voice), played by Pierre Coffin.
Gru(voice)(uncredited), played by Steve Carell.
Despicable Me is an American media franchise created by
Sergio Pablos, Cinco Paul and Ken Daurio.
It centers on a supervillain turned secret agent named Gru, his adoptive
daughters, Margo, Edith, and Agnes, and his yellow-colored Minions.
The franchise is produced by Illumination and distributed
by its parent company Universal Pictures.
The franchise began with the 2010 film of the same name, which was followed by three sequels, Despicable Me 2 (2013), Despicable Me
3 (2017), and Despicable Me 4 (2024) and two spin-off prequels, Minions (2015) and Minions: The Rise of Gru (2022).
The franchise also includes many short films, a television special,
several video games, and a theme park attraction.
The film explores themes of madcap comedy, mailroom, short film.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.